Okay, let's start with the introduction.
First of all, we need to make an internal package gift box, so we need to create a rectangular board.
After creating a rectangular board, we need to select the board outline expansion.
After the board outline expansion, we input the diameter value here, which is the actual expansion of the board outline.
We need to remember to select the corner of the board outline here, so that we can make it a three-dimensional box when it is sewed on the side.
It's like making a handmade paper box in real life.
And don't forget to select the production internal line, because later we will use these internal lines to fold.
After we start the simulation, we can use the fold arrangement tool.
Remember, this is the fold arrangement tool.
After selecting the internal line,
we can quickly fold it into a shape similar to a paper box.
After that, we can see that its folding angle has changed, so we can select this other internal line at the same time.
Set the folding angle on the internal line of the board, and then print it.
After printing the board, you can see that after printing the board, its folding effect will be more obvious.
Then we can sew the side with the sewing line tool.
After opening the simulation, you can see that it is like a folding paper box, because we sewed the sides together.
After sewing, its sides will be connected together.
But because we didn't set the folding angle for the sewing line,
it can't make a very obvious folding effect at the bottom.
So now we need to use the editing sewing line tool
to set the folding angle for the sewing line on the side.
Here, we need to pay attention to the setting of the folding angle.
Our board detects the folding angle based on the front of the board.
So when our folding angle is less than 180 degrees,
this line, whether it is the sewing line or the internal line,
will be highlighted from the front of the board.
If its value is greater than 180,
which is between 180 and 360,
then this line will be folded inward.
Now we can look at this board.
The back of this board is facing outward,
so our folding angle is greater than 180 degrees.
As you can see,
because we didn't use the thickness display,
the back of the board is black in the case of one-sided display.
So now we need to set the sewing line on the side
to set a folding angle greater than 180 degrees,
which is 270 degrees.
After setting the folding angle to 270 degrees,
turn on the simulation again.
Now it will be folded into a square paper box.
Then we can create its lid
according to the rectangular size of the previous creation.
The width and width of the lid of this gift box,
i.e. the width and height of the lid of the gift box,
is slightly larger than the rectangular size.
We can compare it with the rectangular size of the center of the board at the bottom.
Then we can continue to use the expansion of the outside of the board mentioned earlier
to make the four boards on the side.
Then fold it inward.
After folding,
we need to pay attention here,
because now the lid board is different from the bottom board.
The lid board is facing the outside,
so the folding angle of these lines on the lid board
should be less than 180 degrees.
And because we want it to be folded into a rectangle,
so the folding angle of these sewing lines
must be set to 90 degrees,
so that it will be folded into a rectangle.
After that, let's take a look again.
Sometimes,
we don't want the fold angle of this board
to be so obvious,
a very steep fold angle of 90 degrees.
So we will cancel the hardening of the board first,
and then use the bending strength of the board
to make the board still stand on the ground.
Because we can't say that we will always hardening the board.
Of course, if you continue,
as long as you maintain this shape,
you can always hardening this board.
It's just that we can achieve the same result
through physical properties.
Because the function of hardening
actually works in the principle
that the bending strength of the board
changes to about 80%.
That is to say,
our bending strength has a value.
When you hardening a board,
it will add up to an 80% bending strength.
So,
if your board itself is very soft,
after you use hardening,
it looks like it's hardening.
In fact,
it is similar to folding another rectangle.
So,
it is similar to the effect of
folding another material property.
So,
we will cancel the hardening here,
and then go to the material.
It is also possible to
directly and manually increase its bending strength.
Then,
about the fold side,
because after we hardening the board,
its fold effect will be more obvious.
Or,
when our bending strength is increased,
its folding effect will be more obvious.
Here,
we need to set the folding angle
to between 270 and 180 degrees.
Then,
it will not be as hard as before
when we fold it to a 90 degree angle.
Then,
because it is a board
facing the front,
so,
this fold angle
is facing the back.
I just said it wrong.
It is facing the back.
So,
our folding angle
is between 180 and 360 degrees,
which is more than 180 degrees.
Then,
if the fold is as obvious as 270 degrees,
we will choose a number in the middle,
such as
202,
203,
or 204.
Then,
because I don't turn on the single display now,
so,
the front and back display are all white.
In this case,
it may not be convenient for you to watch.
So,
when you usually do these
folding angle settings,
you can switch to the single display
by pressing Alt R.
It will be more convenient to check.
Then,
we can reduce its particle diameter a little bit.
The particle diameter
will also affect
the fold effect.
Because the lower your particle diameter,
the more faces you have,
then,
the position of the fold angle,
because our boards
are all triangular,
in the case of default triangular faces,
it is in the position of some folds and folds,
the triangle
must be the more faces,
the more delicate it is.
Then,
let's create a rectangular board.
This rectangular board is the base board
that we will make
the effect like a tree bag.
We are going to apply a new fabric
to such a board.
Because we have just mentioned
that the board inside
has a very high bending strength attribute,
we will not use such a high bending strength
on the outside board for the time being.
Yes.
Then,
why do we need to use a fixed needle
to drag this board?
Because after that,
we will add a circle of elasticity here.
If we do not take the four corners
of it first,
we will add the elasticity directly after that,
it will not be able to wrap
the support inside very well.
So,
we now have to
take the four corners of it first.
Just like in real life,
we will take the four corners of this fabric
and then add rubber bands in the middle.
In the same way,
we need to remember to reduce the particle diameter.
After that,
we can draw a circle of the inner line
through the inner line diameter function.
In this way,
the outer edge of the outer circle
is equal to the width,
because we are using the inner line diameter.
Then,
you can see that the elasticity
will be tightened in the middle
by applying elasticity.
We can make the center
tighter and tighter through the proportion.
It is worth noting that,
after we tighten the elasticity
to a certain degree,
you will see that
these places where the rubber bands are added,
because we tighten them in the middle,
this material
may have only half the length
as it is now.
Now,
we forcefully lengthen it
to this attribute,
you will see that
the rubber bands on this side
will be stretched very, very long.
This is not stable.
So,
we can remove these
fixed pins first,
because we have already tightened
enough for the opening.
After that,
we can adjust its proportion
and it will not affect
these outer plates.
After removing the fixed pins,
we can see that
now,
these plates are all soft,
so we have to adjust
its physical properties.
Here,
we will use a default material attribute,
which is called silk organza.
It is made of eucalyptus.
The bending intensity of eucalyptus
is about 50.
So,
it will not be as hard as hardwood,
but it also has a certain support.
Under such physical properties,
we can see that
the fabric will have
a certain support.
It will slowly let the
crumpled fabric
stand up.
It will not be as soft
as the fabric attribute just now,
directly on the ground.
After that,
we can tighten the bending intensity
a little bit,
which means that
the bending intensity ratio
is set to be a little bit smaller.
After tightening,
we can see that
because I have drawn
the elliptic plate at the bottom
by hand,
so I need to
adjust it now.
Because we have a lot of fabric
on the side here,
so now we have to
put the side fabric
inside a little bit.
So,
when we are drawing
this elastic line,
we can adjust
the position of the inner line
of this elastic line.
Here,
I used the center point function.
The center point is that
you can set a reference point.
After that,
no matter whether it is
shrinking or adjusting,
or rotating,
it is all based on
this center point.
It is the point of the double joint
that will make it
a center point.
Okay,
then we will
insert the two ends
of this inner line
into the center point.
This way,
it is similar to
this section of fabric
will be reduced.
You can see that
with these two points
approaching the center,
this part of the fabric
in the middle
is less.
It will be less
on the side
of these folds.
Then,
because we just
outside the circle,
that is,
the center point of the
outer line
is more and more
inside,
then the
fold on both sides
must be more and more.
We can also
drag this point
of the outer
side
of the
fold
into the
center point.
In this way,
we can adjust
this fold
little by little.
Okay,
then,
sometimes
if we draw
this fold
too tightly,
you will see
a corner
Many times you can see that there is a gap between some of the panels and other panels.
No matter how you adjust it, no matter how you drag it out, it still has a gap.
In fact, many times it is because the outer panels are too tight.
We can open the sound image by pressing Alt here.
After opening the sound image, you will see the red part.
The red part is to remind you that you have to treat your own panels well
or treat your virtual model well.
Don't make the clothes outside so tight.
In this case, we definitely need to adjust the panels.
First of all, you can let the elasticity of the area outside a little bit.
In this way, there will be more fabric in the middle to wrap the main body.
So if you are wearing it normally, no matter how you adjust the panel,
it still has a gap inside.
At this time, don't use layers.
Because many friends said that I used layers,
it seems more unstable.
It's because the clothes outside are too tight.
In this case, you still have to force it to wear.
It's definitely not going to work.
You must make it a little more fabric.
Then we will make the opening bag.
There will be a loop.
If you make the opening bag, we don't have to worry about it first.
You can draw a longer version with a similar length.
It doesn't matter.
But remember to reduce its particle diameter.
Because if you draw a longer version, you can draw a longer version with a similar length.
Because if you draw a longer version, you can draw a longer version.
Because the opening bag is much smaller than the inside version.
The particle diameter of this version must be very small.
Otherwise, it won't be able to hold the inside version.
Then we can draw an inner line.
Then fold it up with the folding arrangement tool.
Because when we make a circle,
the fabric is not virtual model.
Then you can't form a ring with the arrangement point.
Then fold this line in the three-dimensional space,
which is to use the folding arrangement tool to fold it.
Then add the fixing pin.
After adding the fixing pin,
print the board.
we can drag its two ends closer.
After dragging it closer,
we can use this steel to fold it.
Because the folding arrangement tool can only be used on the inner line
or on the lining line.
So this is why we add an inner line.
When you add the inner line,
you fold it again,
because it automatically applies the folding angle.
Now here it is a very hard-folding angle.
We delete the inner line,
it can form a circle,
because we applied hardening to it.
It can't form a very round circle now,
but it doesn't matter,
we can adjust it later.
Then the two ends,
we can fold them together.
After the two ends are folded,
we can prepare to put this ring in the position of the opening.
First of all, before this,
I have said that when we are hardening a board,
we actually add a bending intensity to this board.
Then we can change the physical properties of the fabric
to full grain leather.
All of its bending intensities,
all of its bending intensities are 100.
Then it will form a rounder circle.
Because the bending intensity is higher,
it is not easy to bend.
The angle of the circle itself is not easy to bend.
So we increase the bending intensity
to make it form a rounder circle.
Then we will add a golden-line shrinkage to it.
In MD,
the vertical direction is the golden line,
and the horizontal direction is the tail line.
OK.
For your board,
I now want to make it form a bigger circle
so that it is easier to cover the outside of the gift inside.
So I must make it longer in the vertical direction,
so that its circle is longer.
So I will add a shrinkage to it.
This is also convenient for us to put the bag of the opening
in the outer circle of the gift inside.
OK.
Then I now want to make a rounder circle.
Then I now make a simple reference.
I will find that it will still have some differences.
That is, this circle is not long enough.
So we will increase its shrinkage a little bit.
Increase from 120 to 150.
Then drag the fixing pin again.
Let it form a very large circle.
Then put this circle outside the gift inside of us.
And it is 2D.
The golden-line value is 2D.
Because our board, it is 2D.
There is a golden-line direction.
The golden-line direction is the direction of our 4-line line.
It is in your board in the 2D window.
Once it is created,
its vertical direction is the golden line.
The horizontal direction is the final direction.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
I will open a Marvelous Designer.
Oh, I'll open it later.
Sometimes your board,
if it was just created,
Sometimes your board, if it was just created,
you are the level, for example, this one
Because when I created the version, the value direction is the longer one
For example, the version I created now
I created this version horizontally
Then what you want to change is not the slope of the gold image
but the slope of the tail image
So when you usually create
When using the slope of the gold tail image
You can use the edit texture tool
This is the tool
I show this tool here on the mouse
After using it to select the version
You can see the line of thought of the version
Hello, good evening
Let's continue
Because we are going to draw a prize all the time
So we have to speak faster
Then we reduce its slope from 150 to 100 gradually
So we use the slope to make it a wider version
It is convenient for it to be outside the inside of the version
Then we use the slope to tighten it
Because it is now
Stable
The slope is already set outside the inside of the version
It doesn't matter if we use the slope to shrink it
This is also a common method we use
That is, if you don't use layers
You can quickly put a version on the outside of another version
That is, use the slope to turn the outer circle of the version into a larger and wider version
After that, put it on first
Then tighten it slowly with the slope
That's why I just said
You have to reduce the particle diameter of this version from the beginning
Then you can also manually adjust the length and width of this version
Then we can reduce the bending strength from 100 to 80
Because this version of our previous bending strength has always been 100
It is very difficult to bend
It can't do it very naturally with the material inside
Because it's very tight now
According to real life
You have to bend and move along the curve of this line
But if your bending strength has always been 100
It will be like a very hard circle
So we will reduce its bending strength to 80
Or a bending strength below
Then it will cancel its print
Now it can be very stable
After the outer circle
We can make this version thinner
And reduce its particle diameter a little more
Because later we will make this version more and more thin
So we must increase its particle diameter again
So that it has enough face to support it
Wrap the inner layer of the version
After that, we can increase its collision thickness and diffusion thickness
Because the diffusion thickness is able to make this version
It has a thickness effect that the naked eye can see
If you only increase the diffusion thickness
Without increasing the collision thickness
The air wall thickness around this version
Will be smaller than what the naked eye actually sees
Then it will look like
There is a gap between the inside and the inside
So in this case
We have to ensure that its collision
Physical collision
Fits its visual effect
We will at the same time
Increase its diffusion thickness and collision thickness
Yes, bending strength is quite common when making this fabric
Then we will show another effect
This is a square version
But inside it is still a round one
With a flexible mouth
Then the square version
If you draw a flexible mouth
It will form a
A bit like that walking grass
A piece of the head
Then we used the editor round tool
To adjust its surroundings
These round ones
Then we come to the second case
The second case
The second case is similar to the package
That is, we install some rice boxes
It will play a package bag effect
This kind of knotting style
Is what you usually do
Whether it's packaging
Or doing some
When the scene is often
To do an effect
Then let's demonstrate here
How to do these knotting styles
Then first of all, this side
Is my simple adjustment to the version
Because I put one version with a fixed needle
After dragging it over with one foot
I think this version is a bit too big
So I use the inner line
To delete the excess fabric
Then we use the fixed needle
In knotting style
Or in doing these
When you need to set the point
When adjusting the fabric
We will use a lot of fixed needles
After that, we can use a sewing needle
To sew the two points temporarily
Because the fixed needle
It is to fix the panel
In the three-dimensional window
And the sewing needle
Is to fix the panel and the panel
For the time being
Is the grid on two panels
Fixed together
Then we can continue to use the fixed needle
Like in real life
Drag the panel
Because why is the fixed needle
It's easy to use
Just because you can
When you don't need it to move
Add the fixed needle to other places
Then you can also go through
Drag the fixed needle
To adjust the position of the fabric
In the three-dimensional space
So the two points on our side
Will always add the fixed needle
Okay, then I'm going to talk about
A black character
That is, we are in real life
To fold this one
When these shapes are wrapped
We will use our hands to pinch it
On both sides
Put this fabric
The pleats on this side will pinch a little bit
Right
In our software
If you are not familiar with physical properties
We can use a
Way to save the country
That is, we can use negative pressure
Pressure is like this
Pressure is actually a kind of fixed force
Pressure in the case of positive pressure
It has the back of the panel
There is definitely a force on the front
Let it be like a pungent effect
So when we are doing those
When the pattern is made
Will give the panel some pressure
For example, the pressure of the positive side
To make it face out
That negative pressure
It is the opposite of the positive pressure
It is to make a panel
Steadily receive
A force from the front to the back
That is to say
It will take your panel
Press from the front to the back
In this case
We now have this panel
Because we are facing the back
So now we are going to use the positive pressure
The pressure of the positive side
Is this fabric
It will have a force
Steadily from the back to the front
To use
Then you can see
After I added the pressure of the positive side
This panel
It will be squeezed very thin
That's because we are now giving it
A pressure
Right
After adding the pressure
We fold it again
But the pressure I added here is the same
Don't give too much pressure
It's just that the pressure can't be too big
Then we can be like in real life
Give it some fixed needles first
Put the side
Because in our real life
I went to study
How others fold this package
They all put the side material first
Give it in
So we are here
Also use fixed needles
To imitate real life
Just like this
Just give it some more fixed needles
To let it
The position where it should be folded
Put it in first
Oh
If you give 1 a lot of pressure
You can
In this
Click on the triangle next to the pressure
Oh
Wait a minute
I'd better look at a Marvelous Designer
I look at a Marvelous Designer
So it's more convenient for everyone to talk about
The functions in our software
Ok
Now we can see Marvelous designer
That is right
Just as everyone said
The press
She's in
You set the software directly
Set as one
It will also have a big discount
Then in this case
First a pressure Effective value
We can click on the triangle on the left
Then we can count
That is the number after the heading
You can do
Align the pressure balance
this can make it not so much pressure and then I just have to talk about it because pressure it is a
from the back side of the board to the front side of a force that the board itself it will still have some properties
affect it the effect of this force is the same as this physical property in real life in this case
should be our density is its weight and weight is affected because the weight is a board
it has always been affected so you face this force you if sometimes you have a board
it is in the three-dimensional space but you do not want to change the weight of the situation you can let
its pressure and the weight of it balance it can be in the three-dimensional space then
do some counterweight effect in addition to the other it and there is one is our board
you are under a pressure when it in addition to our this
the density I just mentioned will be affected, and the strength of the fascia.
If the strength of the fascia is very large,
because we all know that the strength of the fascia controls the tension of the toe line,
it has a stretching effect.
The higher the stretch performance, the more difficult it is to stretch.
Under the same pressure,
if we increase its strength of the fascia to a higher value,
because its stretching performance is very poor,
it is not easy to stretch due to external forces or other forces such as gravity.
Under the same pressure,
you will see that its effect is not as strong as when the strength of the fascia is relatively low.
This will also affect the pressure effect.
So in fact, the same pressure value
will also be due to the different material properties.
So in fact, the same pressure value will also be due to the different material properties.
Let's go back to what we were talking about.
There is a playback.
You can watch the recording later.
I will continue to use the fixed needle to tighten the position of the bag.
In Marvelous Designer,
if you want to make a knot with your hand,
it will be more troublesome.
Because you first need to change the friction force,
and you need to adjust the tension of the band.
If you just make one knot,
it will still be more convenient.
If you need to make a butterfly knot,
or make a twist knot,
I recommend you to do a knot with a fake knot here.
For example,
first of all,
the effect that affects the knot must be this knot.
It has to be more tight.
Because in the end I did a tight knot.
If you just want to make a knot,
You don't have to pull it as tight as I do with a fixed needle.
How to judge if it is tight?
Look at this fold, it's all in one direction.
For example, my folds are all in the horizontal direction in the current three-dimensional space.
In fact, I will prove that the position of the fixed needle is very close to the outside.
Because our fabric is loose in other places.
But now it's going in one direction.
That means it's very thin in the horizontal direction.
In this case, we're going to make it tight.
In its middle line, you can see that I often go to the next point of our board.
That's because I want to look at this blue point, which is the reference point.
Its position is now in this position.
So I'm going to find this blue point in the second level window.
Draw an inner line in the position.
After drawing, I will draw another inner line in the position that is almost the same as it above.
This is the end of this video.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
After that, we can cut this board off along these two inner lines.
Yes, yes.
After that, we can reactivate the two sides of the board.
Then sew it up in the middle.
And then because we just cut the board.
After cutting the board, because of us.
This is what you would ask before.
Why do I have a fixed needle on the board?
But after I did some operations, the position of this fixed needle changed.
Because the fixed needle is a tool added to the grid peak.
When we cut the board, it will cause the grid of the board to re-arrange.
In the case of re-arranging the grid of the board, the original grid peak.
It may be because of some operations.
For example, this grid peak has moved and changed.
For example, when you reduce the particle diameter, you will find that the fixed needle was originally added to a whole piece.
After you reduce the particle diameter, it becomes one by one.
In fact, it is because it was originally followed by the grid peak of the fixed needle.
After your particle diameter is reduced, it will have more grid peaks.
But these grid peaks are not fixed on the top.
This is why we remind everyone.
If you want to reduce the particle diameter, you first delete the fixed needle and then reduce the particle diameter.
Then add the fixed needle back.
Otherwise, the new points added are because you have reduced the particle diameter.
The new grid peaks on top.
It doesn't have a fixed needle.
That's why it looks like there's a secret fixed needle on top.
That's why you cut the board and the fixed needle is gone.
It's because it's out of grid peaks.
The fixed needle will disappear.
So we're going to re-create some fixed needles after we cut it.
And then we're going to put this grid of the board together.
After we put it together, I'm going to use the GPU module all the time.
The GPU simulation is very fast.
And then the simulation is pretty good.
It's a lot better than before.
So I'm doing this now.
If you need to reduce the particle diameter in the early stage to a very small situation, I usually just use the GPU module.
After I sew it up in the middle, I'll just use the elastic ratio to imitate it.
It's a tightening effect.
Reduce the ratio of the elastic ratio a little bit.
That's a basic twist.
In the middle.
We're just going to add two small ears.
And then add the knot in the middle.
It's going to imitate a twist effect.
All right.
Well, because I'm in the middle now.
It's a pinch.
We have another way.
That is, if you want to do the twist in real life.
The effect of turning over.
Because I started with the left side.
Sew the right side.
This is from top to bottom.
Sewing from top to bottom.
That's the twist in real life.
It's definitely going to have a twist.
So I'm going to do a twist on the sewing line here.
Control B is to turn over the sewing line.
After the twist.
You can manually adjust it a little bit.
Because of the GPU simulation.
When it's calculating conflict.
It's not going to be like CPU simulation.
To be very, very, very, very.
In line with this physical attribute.
This is also one of the advantages of GPU simulation.
You can let it when you're modeling.
A little bit of a gap.
It's still a very stable simulation.
And then you manually adjust it.
And then you drag it.
You'll see it in the middle.
It's going to be like a twist in real life.
Turned over.
It's going to be a little bit more real.
Of course, if you're like before.
Left and right.
It's the same way.
It's possible.
It's just that I'm more likely to think.
The effect of this flip may be a little bit better.
And then?
We're just going to have two small ears.
The half is also sewed up.
And then set it up.
In the middle.
I used a fake sewing needle.
Just put them together.
I actually don't put these two.
The half and the bottom of the half are sewn together.
I usually use a fake sewing needle.
Just fix a point.
Because if you want to sew.
One is.
It's hard for you to find it.
Where is the line?
Where?
We're going to do it anyway.
I'm going to use a band.
I'm going to sew it up in the middle.
So you just need to use a fake sewing.
Just make it a temporary fix.
Yeah.
After that.
I thought about it.
It seems to have also given him a flexible.
Let him put it together in the middle.
And then.
The fake sewing needle used in the middle of the two half pieces.
I think it's all.
I just wanted to say.
I'll tell you about it here.
And then in the middle of the bag.
It's just that you can see that I'm a very long bag.
It's actually the same as the bag I just made.
It's the same.
Make him a longer version first.
We can slowly tighten it up later.
Closed up.
This is actually a little bit.
Slowly.
This version of the collection.
In the middle of this version.
I'll give him a harder material.
For example, it's full grain leather.
Or it's.
Fusible Ridge.
It's the beginning of the trim.
I'm using full grain leather here.
I'll change it to Fusible Ridge later.
Fusible Ridge.
This fabric.
Because of its poor stretching performance.
Its tail.
Because it has a relatively high strength.
That's why it's not easy to be transformed by external forces.
Or his stretching performance.
The worse it is, the easier it is to maintain its original shape.
Then he can let the knot here.
Handle it for him.
Tighten it up into a more flat area.
You can see that there are wrinkles all around.
This version.
Because we just gave him the one.
The more solid fabric.
It's not easy.
Like around.
Give birth to so many wrinkles.
Then we.
Through this version.
Go over it.
Form a more flat area.
After that.
We're outside again.
Use the fabric.
To make a false knot.
It's going to be more convenient.
So we can avoid.
Some of the inconvenient problems of manual knotting.
So how do you do this knot?
I used to have a triangle scarf.
Tutorial.
You can just go to that tutorial.
Just look at it.
This knot is done very quickly.
You're creating a rectangular version.
Then the dragon layer.
Then turn the surface over.
The outer layer.
That's it.
Okay.
And then about him.
This side of the board.
Because now we're going to.
It's divided directly into four parts.
So we're going to adjust this.
The length of the knot.
Long and short.
We can just.
Adjust independently.
These two knots.
The shape of the ear board.
Use this method.
Because we're at the base.
It's like turning it into four pieces.
To adjust.
We won't be like a real knot.
If you want to change it a little bit.
It might affect a lot of other parts.
Okay.
Finally, we're going to talk about one.
That kind of butterfly knot production.
That's the gift box.
What are the flowers on it?
How to do it.
First of all.
We already have a basic rectangular ribbon.
This is also very simple.
You just.
Draw a rectangle directly.
And then just.
Just hold it.
And then we're going to.
Give him a rectangular board first.
And then use the function of moving to the sewed board.
So you can make a quick arrangement.
After arranging.
Give him a new fabric.
That's also a regular operation.
Reduce its particle diameter a little bit.
And also reduce the thickness of the gap.
It's a little bit more detailed today.
Maybe draw.
Wait a minute.
It's a little bit late.
Draw a corner.
Okay.
As for us.
After sewing.
You have to pay attention.
Let's freeze the bottom of the board first.
Here we are sewing.
So in the end.
They will be in the same place.
When sewing.
We can put his sewing line type.
Changed from pin sewing to folding.
Folding can make it in the middle.
The position of the sewing is flattened.
You can see it just now.
It's bone.
Now we're going to use the fold.
He's going to flatten it.
It's going to be a little bit more stable.
Folding will let them identify.
Two layers.
So we're going to go along the seam line.
Flatten it.
For us.
Wait a minute.
It's going to add a lot of layers in the middle.
Change it to a fold.
It's going to be better.
And then we can bend it.
Increase the strength.
After increasing the bending strength.
Like I said before.
It's not easy to bend.
It's going to look like a little bit harder.
A hard, thick fabric.
And then use the colon.
The function of the colon.
The symmetrical panel.
Just put it on the other side of the ear.
And then it's also a seam.
After sewing.
Remember to change his sewing line type.
Changed to folding.
And then to make it better.
To simulate better.
We can untie the frozen panel.
And then simulate it again.
After that.
We can copy and paste it.
And then put this little ear panel.
Continue to create.
In addition.
We are adjusting.
If you want to adjust its shape.
Be sure to pay attention.
We usually adjust its length.
Because it's folded now.
So when you extend the panel.
It will have a gap with other panels.
If you adjust it too much.
It may not be stable.
Let's be a little patient.
Adjust it little by little.
Then because we will wait.
On this panel.
Go to stack other panels.
If you think the bending strength is relatively high.
You can adjust the bending strength appropriately.
All a little lower.
And then here.
I'll give you another detail.
When we adjust any properties.
This one.
Because in our real life.
The gold sand and the silver sand.
It's all real.
The diagonal line.
It actually means.
A way of arrangement.
In real life.
The clothes you wear.
Now you can wake up.
That is.
The clothes you wear.
You can go.
Take off your clothes.
You can go in the vertical direction.
And then in the horizontal direction.
Take off your clothes.
In our general situation.
Your clothes.
Because people are all tall and fat.
The total length of his clothes.
It won't become very.
It's a big difference.
So in our vertical direction.
You pull your clothes.
It's all.
Not in the horizontal direction.
It's so easy to pull.
Because we people may.
Eat a little rice or something.
That's the clothes.
You might just have to relax a little bit.
So the horizontal direction.
Pull your clothes.
It's all easier to pull.
It's all flexible.
And then in the vertical direction.
It's not as easy to pull in the horizontal direction.
And then you can go along the diagonal.
To drag your clothes.
Just pull your clothes diagonally.
You'll find your clothes.
Because of its arrangement.
It's in the vertical direction.
And in the horizontal direction.
It's all sand.
The diagonal.
It's just a.
Um.
Arrangement.
It's not a sand line.
So when you pull your clothes diagonally.
You'll find your clothes.
It's best to pull diagonally.
So in Loveless Designer.
Our physical properties.
Your level.
And the value.
That's our gold sand.
And the tail of the sand.
The physical properties of the gold and the tail.
Its value is greater than.
It's in the vertical direction.
So usually.
You're in.
When you're setting physical properties.
When you're manually adjusting physical properties.
You can pay a little attention.
If you don't know.
How much value the diagonal line is going to give.
You can use the level.
Refer to the level.
And the value of the value direction.
And then reduce the two values a little bit.
Just fill in the position of the diagonal line.
All right.
And then.
We're going to copy it.
Two small ears.
Keep sewing on top of it.
Oh, don't forget.
We're going to change the type of the sewing line.
Folding.
And then there's one more thing to note.
That's what we usually do when we sew.
Don't cross-sew when you're sewing.
What does it mean to cross-sew?
He's got two little ears now.
Right?
We're going to put it together with the one that's closest to him.
Don't cross over the middle layer.
Just sew the ugly part at the bottom.
It's not going to be stable.
Don't cross-sew.
So usually.
When you're sewing, you're going to have to follow the old-fashioned principle.
To sew the one that's closest to him.
All right.
And then.
Because we just made some adjustments to his physical properties.
You can adjust it manually afterwards.
The more layers you stack on top of it.
His curve and.
This shape will also change slowly.
Then we can add layers one by one.
That's it.
Finally, we can create a cut-off plate.
Then we can sew it up in the middle.
Then we can create a cut-off plate.
If you're sewing n to n.
It's the first part.
And then.
It's 1 to n.
The whole part is first sewn.
Is the cut-off plate we have now.
Then press the shift key.
Sew from the first part.
Select the other side and then release the SHIFT key to complete it.
Yes, yes, yes.
For this layer, we want to lower its particle diameter a little bit.
As we talked about before,
the smaller the particle diameter of the outer layer,
the better it will be.
Then you can untangle it and simulate it again.
This is the effect we usually see.
In addition to this,
there is another one that we made on the promotional poster.
It's like a embroidered ball.
We are going to draw the inner line on this group of panels first.
When drawing the inner line,
we can press the SHIFT key to open the reference line,
then press the right key
to open the window setting.
We can create a multi-sided window setting.
We just need to open the mirror depth.
Then we can draw some inner line lines along the 45 degree angle.
Of course, you don't need to draw it as accurately as I do.
You can draw a general inner line as well.
After drawing,
we can copy and paste this group of small earplugs.
OK.
After copying and pasting this group of small earplugs,
we are going to start to sew it together with the bottom layer of this group of small earplugs.
When sewing,
we first sew the left and right two small earplugs together.
Then add a fixing pin to them.
Let's simulate it first.
Then we can adjust it again in the 3D space.
Let's put this small earplug.
It's just to put it diagonally with the bottom like this.
Then you can use 3D sewing.
Just sew it in the 3D window.
Adjust the sewing line.
This is more intuitive than sewing directly in the 2D.
Just sew this line in the middle to the top of our inner line.
Because I've tried it.
Just like I said before.
When I was making the package,
I didn't sew the small earplugs together with the bottom layer.
That's because
there will be an opening on the outside.
But because we made this ball at the end,
it doesn't have the opening in the middle.
So we can't use a sewing needle here.
You may have to use the inner line to sew it together.
This is the effect of our last sewing ball.
You can see that I have pasted a lot of groups here.
And in the middle, I sewed two pieces separately.
That's all about the content of our gift packaging.